easyfinance.com 2013-05-21

# EasyFinance.com Privacy Policy for Consumers - EasyFinance.com

**Your Privacy Rights**

**Last Updated: 3/28/2013**

This website is owned and operated by EasyFinance.com. We want you to understand what information we gather about you; how we use it and the safeguards we have in place to protect it.  This Privacy Policy applies to information collected through this website and otherwise.   This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with information that we collect through this website owned and controlled by us which display or link to this Privacy Policy (the “Site”).  By using our Sites, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.  

**Who We Are and What We Do**

EasyFinance.com (“EasyFinance”) operates a prospective customer database ("Service") by which it compiles, sorts and sells contact information to businesses on behalf of individual consumers who have shown an interest in applying for a business' products or services and has affirmatively asked to be contacted by a representative of a product or service business. EasyFinance.com utilizes third party vendors, third party affiliates, and a variety of media advertisements to promote the Site to consumers interested in completing an online application at our Site or to supplement our database by purchasing their database of consumers who have completed applications on websites other than EasyFinance's and have affirmatively requested receipt of information about product or service offerings similar to those offered on EasyFinance's Site. 

EasyFinance also promotes its product and service offerings via e-mail or telephone to consumers who requested that they be contacted either through our online application opt-in process via our Site or through an Opt-In process on one of our many vendor or affiliate sites (List Members). List Members will then receive email or telephone contacts only for so long as they wish to continue to receive such contacts. 

List Members can get off our telephone and e-mail contact lists at any time, no questions asked. You can remove yourself from further contact from EasyFinance by clicking on the OPT-Out link contained in each e-mail, or by sending in your OPT-Out request via e-mail to office@easyfinance.com. 

If you choose to remove yourself from our contact list, if applicable, we will also forward your name and contact information to the specific vendor or affiliate marketer who provided your informational request to us so that they can include your name on their do-not-contact list too. Please bear in mind that if your information was purchased commercially from a third party vendor, EasyFinance may not be the only data EasyFinance your contact information was sold to. Additionally, our third party vendor or affiliate may have purchased your contact information from someone else and thus you may continue to receive contacts.html from those companies as well. EasyFinance is not responsible for stopping all unwanted contacts.html from sources beyond our immediate control. 

**Your Privacy is Our Concern**

We recognize the importance of protecting your personal information. We collect and retain information about you to communicate with you, to process your requests for products and services, and to inform you about other financial services that may be of interest to you through our newsletter. Except as explained here in our Privacy Policy, we do not sell nonpublic personal information about current or former customers, nor do we share this type of information with anyone other than our affiliates. The examples in this Privacy Policy are illustrative only and are not intended to be exclusive. 

We want consumers to feel comfortable using the Site and participating in the Service, so we have created this Privacy Policy to let you know what information we may collect from you on the Site and through the Service and how we may use that information. Please take a moment to review the terms of our Privacy Policy. By using the Site and participating in the Service, you agree to accept the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site or participate in the Service. 

Minors

This website is a general audience site and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. 

**What does Easyfinance .com do with your personal information?**

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or your loan request. This information can include:

  * Social Security number and income, name, address, telephone number, email address, driver's license number, military status, information about your spouse or dependent, identification of individuals close to you such as your job supervisor
  * banking account information, ABA/Routing numbers, and employment information
  * credit history and assets including whether you rent or own, income source, how you get paid, how often you get paid, length of time with employer and bank, and next two pay dates
  * IP address, browsing and log data, your desired loan amount and any other information that may be required in a loan application

We use cookies to allow faster and easier access to your account information, monitor traffic on the site and measure traffic patterns to improve the website. We

may combine personal information we collect from you with other information about you that we receive from third party sources, such as to ensure our loan matching application records are accurate.

**Access to Loan Information**

We have access to your personal and financial information when you inquire about a loan application.  When providing your Application information to loan marketing affiliates and lenders, we may provide a substitute e-mail address to the lender as your e-mail address to reduce the potential for unwanted e-mails and spam.

You understand that through this substitute e-mail address, we may have access to information regarding any loan made to you by a Lender or other correspondence sent to you by the Lender. We may also, at any time, provide Lenders with the actual e-mail address you provided on your Application. We do not use information in responses from the Lender except to route such information to you.

**General Information Collection and Use**

EasyFinance.com collects information through the Site from our prospective and existing customers at several different points on our web sites. We use contact information to send information about EasyFinance and to service existing accounts. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Contact and Financial information that is collected is used for verifying your name, address and other information. Not all information asked for on our site is required when you fill out our forms. Only Name, City, State, Address, Zip Code, Work Phone, Home Phone, Email Address, House Type, Current Value, Loan Amount Desired, 1st Mortgage Balance, Current Interest Rate, Current Payment, Are you Behind on Payments, Credit Rating, Place of Employment, Years Employed, Yearly Income, Loan Desired, and Best Time to Call. Information about your computer hardware and software is automatically collected by EasyFinance.com and may be shared in aggregate with third parties whose services are used for traffic analysis purposes. This information includes: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by EasyFinance.com to maintain and improve the quality of the service and to generate statistics regarding use of the EasyFinance.com site.  EasyFinance.com does not use third party databases to correct or update the information you submit to us for any reason. 

To maximum friendly our site usage you don't need to complete any registration forms. 

Choice/Opt-Out.

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners as previously described above. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

You can send e-mail to office@EasyFinance.com.

You can send mail to the following postal address: 

EasyFinance.com

3450 Sacramento Street

San Francisco, CA 94118

Please note that participation in certain activities on our web site may be limited if personally identifiable information is not submitted for the user. E-mail addresses and phone numbers received in an opt-out request will be added to our internal Do-Not-Contact registry within ten (10) Business days following receipt. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site however without cookies the user may not have access to certain features on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. All cookies served on the domain, both session and persistent are tied to the Personally Identifiable Information you provide. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies once set on our site. 

**Links**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that EasyFinance is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by EasyFinance even in cases where we may frame another site with our own. From time to time we may co-brand certain services with third parties. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting such information and whose privacy statement governs. For example, without limiting the foregoing, we co-brand with insurance brokers, credit reporting agencies and, automotive companies. 

**Security**

We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. 

**Disclosure**

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Agreement. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances as required by law, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. 

In addition, as noted above, if you opt-out of future contact from EasyFinance by using the opt-out mechanism provided in each e-mail we send to you on behalf of a third party service provider other than EasyFinance, we will provide your email address to the third party service provider so that the third party service provider can add your name and contact information to its own do-not-contact list. 

As EasyFinance grow, we may buy other businesses or their assets or sell our business assets. Customer information is generally one of the business assets involved in such transactions. Thus, in the event that EasyFinance or all of its assets are acquired, customer information, including any visitor information collected through the Site, would be one of the transferred assets. For more information see our Notification of Changes section below. 

Finally, EasyFinance reserves the right to disclose member information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) EasyFinance’s rights or property, other visitors, members, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. EasyFinance also reserves the right to disclose visitor or member information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

**Sharing Information with Affiliates**

When you submit your request for information or quote, you are granting permission to be contacted by EasyFinance.com or affiliated third parties. We share the contact and loan request data you submit on the Quote Request form and EasyFinance.com account number information with affiliated companies such as banks, commercial lenders and licensed loan brokers to fulfill information requests we receive from you, to provide you with superior service, inform you of product and service opportunities that may be of interest to you, and for other business purposes, we may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to the following types of affiliated companies: financial service providers, such as mortgage and life insurance agencies, title service companies, debt & credit services companies and auto finance companies. An affiliate company is a company under legal contract with EasyFinance.com to fulfill services or is a company owned in whole or in part by EasyFinance.com. 

**Sharing Information with Co-Branded Partners**

We may share, license or sell your information to third parties for various marketing purposes, including their online (e.g., e-mail marketing) and offline (e.g., telemarketing, cell phone text messaging, skip tracing, outbound calls and or robo-dialing, and direct mail) marketing programs. By filling out or submitting a registration form or partial registration form you are consenting to receive offers from us and third marketers via email, telemarketing postal mail and or SMS text message wireless or other mobile offering to your cell phone. You understand that your wireless carrier’s standard charges and rates apply to these messages. For SMS text messages, you may remove our information by replying “STOP”, “END”, OR “QUIT” to the SMS text message you have received and we will remove your personal information within 10 days of receiving such request.

Some of the services offered on our website are co-branded with contracted partners. Co-Branded offerings will be identified directly on the Quote Request form for the product or service you choose prior to you having to submit the Quote Request. Where a co-branded product or service provider is identified your Personally Identifiable information will be provided directly to that providers website, not EasyFinance.com. The Product or Service provider shall control your data once submitted to them. For purposes of identification and tracking, your contact information (name, Address, Phone, e-mail address, etc.) is shared with EasyFinance.com. 

We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider's standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence. You may opt-out and remove your SMS information by sending "STOP," "END," "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received. If you remove your SMS information from our database it will no longer be used by us for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by EasyFinance.com or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you. 

**Do Not Call Registry Compliance**

By submitting personal contact and/or financial information, the user hereby grants written permission to EasyFinance.com, its affiliated sites, and its business partners for contact via telephone, mail, and/or e-mail. Further, by registering at EasyFinance.com you are consenting to receive phone calls from EasyFinance.com, its affiliated sites, and its business partners for contact via telephone, including but not limited to lenders that may contact you regarding a loan and thereby registrants waive their right to file a claim with the FTC or any other agency in reference to these calls or contacts. 

**Our Former Customers**

We treat information about our former customers in the same manner as we treat information about our current customers. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information against unauthorized access or use. 

Maintaining the accuracy of your information is a shared responsibility. We maintain the integrity of the information you provide us and will update your records when you notify us of a change. Please contact us at the address or phone number listed below when information concerning you changes. 

**Site and Service Updates**

We will send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We also communicate with user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to the account via e-mail or telephone when requested. 

**Notification of Changes**

If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will prominently post a notice on the website for 30 days. We may also make a reasonable effort to notify users by way of an email. Users have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this materially different manner. 

**Correct/Update Information**

If you would like to verify any data that we have received from you, make any corrections or disable the use of your personal information, please contact us at office@EasyFinance.com

Our address: 

EasyFinance.com

3450 Sacramento Street

San Francisco, CA 94118

office@EasyFinance.com
